let quiz=[
    {
      question: "Java was inroduced by among which of the following organizations :",
      option: [
           "Sun Microsystem",
           "IBM",
           "Intel",
           "Microsoft",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "LAN can be connected by which of the following devices which operates on the data link layer :",
      option: [
           "Hub",
           "Bridges",
           "HDLC",
           "Tunnel",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is the fastest media of data transfer :",
      option: [
           "Co-axial cable",
           "Untwisted wire",
           "Telephone lines",
           "Fiber Optic",
      ],
       answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the maximum limit of free cloud storage on Google drive :",
      option: [
           "2 GB",
           "10 GB",
           "15 GB",
           "20 GB",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What is a firewall in computer network :",
      option: [
           "The physical boundary of network",
           "An operating system of computer network",
           "A system designed to prevent unauthorized access",
           "A web browsing software",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "A person who uses his expertise for develop a software is known as :",
      option: [
           "Programmer",
           "Security Hacker",
           "Analyst",
           "None of the above",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Keys used for performing specific tasks are known as :",
      option: [
           "Toggle key",
           "Modifier key",
           "Function key",
           "Alphanumeric key",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Total number of pins present in VGA cable are :",
      option: [
           "15",
           "20",
           "150",
           "10",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is Koo :",
      option: [
           "Short film on environment degradation",
           "Micro blogging app developed by Indians",
           "An endangered species of a bird",
           "An award winning Nobel",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is Param Siddhi :",
      option: [
           "India's AI supercomputer",
           "An unique project of 'Siddha'-a part of Ayush system of medicine",
           "A supersonic missile",
           "An electric locomotive developed by RDSO",
      ],
      answer: 1 ,
    },
    {
  question: "Which of the following issues are related to the software aging ?",
  option: [
  "Quality of Software decreases",
  "Entropy of software increases",
  "Both (A) and (B)",
  "None of the above",
  ],
  answer: 3, 
},
{
  question: "First Cyber law which provides the legal infrastructure for e-commerce in India is :",
  option: [
  "The Information Technology Act,1996",
  "The Information Technology Act,2000",
  "The Information Technology Act,1998",
  "The Information Technology Act,1990",
  ],
  answer: 2, 
},
{
  question: "Bibliometry is :",
  option: [
  "Function of Library network",
  "Information Management Service",
  "Information Management Tool",
  "Library Service",
  ],
  answer: 3, 
},
{
  question: "The keyword Used to transfer control from a function back to function (in C) is :",
  option: [
  "go back",
  "Switch",
  "goto",
  "Return",
  ],
  answer: 4, 
},
{
  question: "Which header file should be included to use functions like malloc() and calloc() ?",
  option: [
  "memory.h",
  "stdlib.h",
  "string.h",
  "dos.h",
  ],
  answer: 2, 
},
    ]  
